Who is this?
I've never seen him before.
Good afternoon, sir.
I'm Kinoto, the architect you spoke
on the phone with earlier today.
I'm here to assess the fire
restoration and renovation.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
We did agree to meet.
I'm in store! Attack!
My apologies for the forceful
greeting, but one has to be cautious.
I see, born a 1970 top-notch
architect named Masazo Kinoto.
He's definitely the one I called for
repairs, and he doesn't seem to be a threat.
That's peculiar.
Then again, no one's without
their bizarre fears and phobias.
At any rate, he seems safe
enough to let into the house.
Though that Ro-sham brat
also seemed innocent.
A simple command of I can't attack
Rohan should suffice for now.
Oh my, I'm so sorry.
Did I just make a faux pas?
Not at all.
Come in and we'll talk.
We have a lot to discuss.
Is something the matter?
Most of the damage is in here.
You can't perform a proper
assessment from out there.
Oh, no.
Please go on ahead.
I'll be right behind you, sir.
Now, where is that room?
I'd love to see it.
I didn't think my escape
would go so smoothly.
Though I shouldn't be surprised.
You haven't even caught
Yoshikage Kira yet, have you?
Did it ever cross your mind
that my name might be fake?
Or that I could maybe be wearing a mask?
Does the name Kanedaichi sound real? What?
This guy's a fake?
So you've been wearing
a gaudy mask all along?
Leaving this place has been my mission.
Did you really think I'd do
it without a clean escape?
See ya, boys!
Then I definitely wouldn't wanna be ya!
Hey! Get back here! No, Mr.
Josuke! Don't come in here!
I shall remain in the tower for now.
You're right!
There's no way we're leaving you in there!
We're only in this situation
because I discovered the tower.
As for this,
it's my fault for deciding to turn
into the power line and climb up here.
I only wanted to be useful.
I wanted to change your opinion
and for you to be proud of me.
I should have just listened to Okuyasu.
I should have stayed out of it.
Don't trouble yourselves.
I am used to the inside of a spaceship,
so this is really quite nice.
You're a weird one but
you've got a lion's heart
though to be frank I
honestly don't give a damn.
Who remains trapped in
here as long as I walk
free I'm a happy man what
you fools do after that
is oh No you're a permanent
resident I remember
you saying something
about not wanting to be us
Once I'm done nobody in their right mind
will want to be you
what why just a piss off
Thanks to you cutting this line, I was
able to fix it and get myself up here.
Damn you!
Mikitaka, give me about ten
seconds and I'll have you free.
After I put this bro hole
back in his douche cage,
I'll heal you up and it'll
be like this never happened.
Be careful up there, Josuke!
Don't you fall!
Yeah, as if.
Props, friend.
Mending the wire to swing
up here was ingenious,
but coming back to this tower was not
the smartest move you could have made.
I would have been perfectly
content leaving this place behind.
In fact, killing you pig-headed
boobs never crossed my mind.
But you just had to go and force my act!
So now for me to make my getaway,
I have no other choice but
to push you to your death!
Go to hell!
You know,
now that I see your shining diamond up
close, it's actually pretty damn impressive.
Even so, you can't really think
you'd stand a chance against me.
I could prance around the top of
this tower with my eyes closed.
And I'm guessing your stance
range is about two meters.
What the hell?
Screw you, dick!
You're gonna pay for that!
Mr.
Josuke, you have to move now!
He's already slashed the
tower with his knife!
Look!
He carved slits into the beam!
That was a real low blow, you know that?
Though to be fair, as
fast as your attacks are,
my shining diamond won't
even break a sweat.
Keep smirking, Preak.
We'll see if you're
still wearing that smile
after the ass-whooping
I'm about to give you.
I know every centimeter of this
tower like the back of my hand,
you loudmouthed shit.
I also know precisely
which angle to cut to
send the projectile in
the direction I desire.
Like a pool shark who's bored
with his own mastery of the game,
I know all the moves! Pool shark?
Josuke, no!
Didn't you just say my
attacks weren't fast
enough to make Shining
Diamond break a sweat?
Let's see if that holds true if you
don't know where they're coming from.
Now, how many shots did I fire back there?
They're ricocheting off
the beams as I speak.
Watch out, they're coming for you!
Mr.
Josuke, behind you!
Mr. Josuke!
Didn't I tell you coming
up here was a dumb move?
Especially after your
alien friend had the balls
to say you'd stay behind
and cover your ass.
If only you'd have listened to him, at
the very least you could have lived.
No, not both of his arms.
There's no way he can
dodge another onslaught.
Now the time's come
for the finishing blow!
I think I'll - Hey
Okuyasu, question for ya.
You saw this guy's
projectile thingies, right?
Did you catch how many of my knocked
away with my shining diamonds?
I'm cooking up something
Yeah,
I saw the whole thing you definitely
managed to land a hit on four
of those suckers How the hell can you
be so nonchalant four of them, huh?
Well, that should be plenty.
I only need four shots to take
you down What are you blathering
on about if I'm remembering right
you use the word ricochet? Yeah,
that's right You said your stand's energy
ricocheted around like billiard balls.
Well, that is what you said, isn't it?
That's right.
What are you going to do about it?
By now, you know my stand
is called Shining Diamond.
But did the old fart in the
photo let you in on the fact
that it can correct destroyed
matter and fractured energy?
Maybe he did, maybe he didn't.
But what's that got to do
with your current predicament?
Are you really telling me you had the
time to correct something just now?
What kind of fool do you take me for?
He corrected the energy
ricocheting between the
beams so that it would
return to the slash steel.
Mr.
Josuke, I thought that you were done
for, but you had already won this battle.
How'd you pull that off?
You said coming up here was a dumb move.
What do you think of my plan now?
Streaming
Please forgive me The whole
reason I started living in
this godforsaken tower was
to get away from other people
But that cranky old grand dude
in the photograph convinced
me to trap a stand user He
said if I could just do that,
he'd make sure I'd be
able to have a life in
the outside world So
I decided to go for it
Please go easy on me
I'm begin' you If you'd
let me go back inside
the safety of my tower,
I'll be a good boy.
I never want to leave home again.
Just let me stay between these beams.
I promise I'll live out the rest
of my life in peace and quiet.
New Mariah Landmark, the
man in the electrical tower.
He's a marvel of self-sufficiency.
But if you bring him a
bit of salt or snacks,
he'll be happy to let you take a picture.
But don't expect him to
be able to muster up the
courage to take off his mask
or divulge his real name.
Yeah, that's fine.
But tell us more about the old guy.
Did he tell you anything else?
Like the whereabouts of
his son Yoshikage Kira.
Anything would help us.
Well, actually, he did
mention a stand user.
I think his name was Koichi.
What else do you know about Koichi?
Hey, take it easy, man.
The geyser and I were just
having some casual conversation.
He barely even mentioned him.
The subject never came up again,
so he didn't think to ask anything,
and he didn't elaborate
on who the guy was.
Get to the point!
What did he say about Koichi?
Well, he told me that he
found a way to eliminate him.
He said he got rid of him?
And if his son's Yoshikage Kira,
then it seems like the old man
might have already caught up to him.
He said from now on, he would do
more than just protect his son.
He'd start seeking out
and attacking his enemies.
Then he told me that a
recently created stand user
eliminated a user named
Koichi just this morning.
But that's all, I swear.
Hmm, and this would be...
Oh, goodness, look at this door!
This'll be about 800,000 yen by itself!
And these designs are from the
Victorian or Edwardian era,
and they even use English-made materials!
This is going to be a Days.
So he doesn't want anyone
looking at his back.
I suppose that could explain his rather
odd behavior when he first arrived.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Before it gets cold.
Oh, I'll be fine.
Now's not the time.
I must resist.
AAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHH?
AAAAAH?
Boy...
I really hope that they
find Koichi safe and sound.
Hmm...
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah!
Gah! GAH!
Come on!
I can't find him at home or at school!
He's disappeared!
Koichi! Koichi!
Where are you, Koichi?
I'm not giving up, you hear me?
I'm gonna do whatever it
takes to find you, Koichi!
That's the long and the short of it.
I wanna know if you're willing
to get off your ass and
help me find Koichi with
your scent-tracking ability?
Yuya Fungami.
If you do, I'll get rid of your injuries.
That's the deal.
I'll say it once understand
don't you mess with me Josuke?
I don't play around and I
won't forgive you for attacking
me like a savage and
landing me back in this bed!
What makes you think I you you Fungami
would sacrifice my pride to help you?
So you're turning me down, huh?
I kind of figured this would
be a long shot Well, see ya.
I'm short on time.
Wait, where are you?
Don't tell me you're gonna leave just
like that Hey, would you wait a sec?
You haven't even given me the
chance to bargain Okay, fine.
Have it your way.
I'll help you find your little friend.
It's not like I actually
have a choice in the matter.
I guess I could hold out
for a better bargain,
but then I'd just be stuck
in this dump even longer.
I can't give my girls the kind of
attention they deserve while I'm like this,
and for all I know, they could be
on their way out of my life forever.
This is so horrible, you know?
And besides, the accident that got me
into this whole mess is my own doing.
I've got nothing against you.
Now, can you hurry up and
get to the healing already?
These injuries are driving me insane!
Quit your complaining!
Shining Diamond!
Already reversed your injuries?
There's that gorgeous face!
I'm a stunningly beautiful
creature, aren't I?
At the very least!
It's like I'm one of Michelangelo's
sculptures come to life,
but now that I'm getting a better look?
Look, I think my eyes
are slightly droopier.
Your stand can actually
fix things 100%, right?
Count your blessings, douche!
Now stop preening in the mirror and tell
me how well your sense of smell works!
Well, let's see.
I can't promise I'd be as good as a
trained hunting dog or anything, but...
Hmm.
For example, I can tell that there are
three girls walking up the hall right now.
It smells like Rock, Akemi, and Yoshi.
They're my fangirls, remember?
Based on their scent, they're
coming back from the pachinko place.
You, babe, what's up?
You, baby, you're out of
that icky hospital bed! Yo!
You, baby, you're back!
You, sweetie!
There, there, everything's fine, vixens.
You're Josuke, aren't you?
Why the hell are you here?
Wanna get skewered right here and now?
Easy, girls.
I hold no ill will toward him.
Um, more importantly, you gals just
got back from Pachinko, yeah? Huh?
How in the world did you know?
Because all of your
skirts reek of ass sweat.
Why else would you be planting those
supple cheeks on vinyl chairs for so long?
Say, Akemi, you got any chocolate?
You wanted Pachinko, didn't you?
Yeah, I did!
You're amazing, you!
Here, we brought you a souvenir!
Now do you see, Josuke?
I am who I am thanks to these
lovely dames in my arms.
Thanks to you, I can hold
them again, so I'll help you.
You said you weren't as
good as a hunting dog.
But as far as I'm concerned,
you're even better.
I'm aware that the upstairs floor
sustained fire damage as well.
I'll perform the estimates,
so please go ahead without me.
What's this man doing?
Why's he so obsessed with hiding his back?
What'll happen if I look?
I have to see it.
How could I not want to
look after that display?
If I have to trick him, then so be it.
Oh, how annoying.
It's so itchy.
If only there was some way or
other, I could reach this itch.
I suppose it would be quite rude of me to
ask a person I just met
to scratch it for me,
huh?
I suppose I don't mind helping.
Right, this is the place.
We found Koichi's bag lying right
here in the open with no explanation.
His house is only about two
minutes up the road there.
How did this new stand user
storm Koichi and snatch
him away from a busy street
first thing in the morning?
Somebody should have seen him.
Chosuke, our little deal doesn't
include me fighting, does it?
Because when I agreed to come here, I was
told that I'd only be used for tracking.
I won't feel comfortable proceeding until
you tell me I won't be fighting anyone.
Why bring something like
that up at a time like this?
Because somebody's been tailing you. What?
It's that man over there.
And that's not all.
I smell Koichi's scent on that man.
Of course.
He must have something on
him that belongs to Koichi.
Are you serious?
That's the guy we're looking for?
Hey, you!
Come back here!
Tell me what you did with
Koichi, you kidnapping bastard!
Mom?
What the hell?
It's definitely Mom.
She's out cold, but she's alive.
I was watching from here and still
don't have a clue what happened.
When did he change into Josuke's mom?
I heard Jotaro can stop
time for a couple seconds,
but this is a new level
of timey-wimey bullshit!
And even Jotaro wouldn't
be able to quickly
swap out one person
with another like that!
If he had just come out and hit me, I
would have been fine with knocking him out?
grabbing Koichi, and calling it a day.
But that bastard went after my mom!
Scum like him needs to be punished!
This scheming scumbag is going down!
Hey, Yuya!
Where's that piece of shit hiding?
I'll make him pay for what he's done!
But how the hell would I know?
You were touching the guy
and managed to lose him!
Wait a second...
He's still here, Josuke?
I'm still picking up a
trace of his scent nearby!
Hmm...
Yuya Fungami, eh?
Who knew a simple nose
would be such a nuisance?
I never dreamed these fools
would sniff me out, as it were.
Either way, releasing Josuke's
mother was all part of the plan.
The perfect plan to observe Josuke.
Observation that's what
my stand mysterioso
does best mysterioso meticulously observe.
Koichi Hirose's movements as well as your
mother's that boy really pisses me off
I'll just help myself
to his that Josuke
so he is home after all show yourself.
No one in the world is
immune to fear you really
shouldn't hide the glow of
fear or the tremors of dread
there's a kind of fear that
lies deep within the soul no
matter what you do it could
You'll never be wiped away,
not ever.
Who are you?
How did you get into my house?
According to my observations,
you tend to swallow your saliva?
when gripped with the
equalizer of unyielding fear.
All people exhibit certain unconscious
behaviors when in a state of panic.
Certain terror-induced quirks
come swirling to the surface.
Did you know about yours?
I don't know if you're a robber or
what, but I'm not giving you any money.
So get the hell out!
Do I look like a common burglar?
I don't want your money.
In fact, it feels like
I should be paying you.
I'm having quite the
exhilarating morning, you see.
Being the recipient of so much
attention is such a lovely treat.
The attention you're showering me
with out of fear is simply wonderful.
Oh, my.
It looks like you just swallowed again.
Ah, you see. I was right.
Yet another swallow.
So that really is the
telltale sign of your fear.
And once I discover your
precious mark of fear,
my Mysterioso comes alive and
unleashes its invincible onslaught!
I've transformed Tomoko
Higashikata and Koichi
Hirose into paper with hardly any effort.
When I startled Koichi
on his way to school,
I discovered his mark of
fear as a double blink,
an obvious tell.
Yuya!
For the last time, where
is the scent coming from?
I imagined,
regardless of Josuke's tough exterior,
plopping his mother before his eyes
would certainly stir up pangs of dread.
Sure enough, there was
Josuke's very own mark.
When he experiences fear, he
anxiously bites his lower lip!
The next time Josuke
reveals his mark of fear,
Mysteriosa will eradicate that
do-gooder once and for all!
Hey, Yuya, you haven't taken
your eyes off my mom, right?
The user.
Is it possible he's inside her jacket?
I don't care what kind of stand it is, I
need to know what's inside this pocket!
Oh, is he gonna bite his lip?
Come on, do it!
Yuya, answer me!
Is he here or not?
Damn, fear hasn't consumed him yet.
We've been over this Josuke.
I never promised to help
you fight any enemies.
We only agreed that I'd track him.
Anymore, and I'd be risking my life.
Besides, I only said I'd
help because you healed me.
There's no way in hell I'm going down as
that dumbass who walks
right into harm's way.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but this guy freaks me out.
Then I'll check for myself.
Nothing.
Both pockets are empty.
Other than this piece of paper.
The scent's out of the pocket now.
Could it be?
No, you fool.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll keep that piece of paper closed.
The face of the humic
and of all that I need
to I want to come stand
a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher you'll
never know what hit you when I get to you!
Oh I want you I don't know if I
need you but oh I gotta find out.
need you but oh I gotta find out?